<news>
	<article>
		<image><img src="nbc.jpg" alt="NBC"/></image>
		<datesource>[11/03/14] NBC NEWS - Crowdsourced Jet Search Overwhelms Satellite Company's Servers</datesource>
		<body>
			<line>A satellite imagery provider is trying to give people all over the world the opportunity to help search for the 
			missing Malaysia Airlines jet — but the demand is proving more than its servers can handle.</line>
			<line>Unfortunately, they were a bit too eager. The Tomnod website has been up and down — mostly down — for much of 
			Tuesday. While DigitalGlobe hasn't released any traffic figures, it must surely be far more than the thousands of 
			people who signed on to flag objects of interest after Typhoon Haiyan. Even the blog post acknowledging the technical 
			difficulties has had trouble loading.</line>
		</body>
		<source><a href="http://www.nbcnews.com/storyline/missing-jet/crowdsourced-jet-search-overwhelms-satellite-companys-servers-n50056">Source</a></source>
	</article>

	<article>
		<image><img src="IBT.jpg" alt="IBT"/></image>
		<datesource>[18/02/14] International Business Times - Obama Says Cyber terrorism Is Country's Biggest Threat</datesource>
		<body>
			<line>"Cybersecurity has become a U.S. government priority in the past year, after a string of denial 
				of service (DOS) attacks on government computers and hacking attempts of the CIA’s main computer, 
				as well as on French, Israeli and British defence agencies. But while many of these sophisticated 
				cyber-attacks have sought to inconvenience governmental agencies that have little impact on day-to-day 
				public life, many in the government are increasingly worried about an attack on the energy sector."</line>
		</body>
		<source><a href="http://www.ibtimes.com/obama-says-cyberterrorism-countrys-biggest-threat-us-government-assembles-cyber-warriors-1556337">Source</a></source>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<image><img src="TI.png" alt="TI"/></image>
		<datesource>[11/02/14] The Independent - World's largest Denial of Service attack caused by vulnerability in the infrastructure of the web</datesource>
		<body>
			<line>"Hackers have exploited a key vulnerability in the infrastructure of the internet to mount what has been described by security 
			researchers as the world’s largest Denial of Service (DoS) attack.</line>
			<line>Hacks of this type are used to overwhelm web services by flooding them with requests for data and are a key weapon in the arsenal 
			of hacking collectives such as Anonymous as well as government bodies.</line>
			<line>The severity of DoS attacks are measured in gigabits-per-second (Gbps), with this recent example tipping 400Gbps – more than 
			100gbps larger than the previous record. The destructive traffic was absorbed by the servers of CloudFlare, a company that specialises 
			in protecting against just such attacks.</line>
			<line>Matthew Prince, the chief executive of CloudFlare, <a href="https://twitter.com/eastdakota/status/433044201807159296">commented on Twitter:</a> 
			“Someone’s got a big, new cannon. Start of ugly things to come.”"</line>
		</body>
		<source><a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/worlds-largest-denial-of-service-attack-caused-by-vulnerability-in-the-infrastructure-of-the-web-9122200.html">Source</a></source>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<image><img src="TR.png" alt="TR"/></image>
		<datesource>[10/02/14] The Register - Snapchat bug lets hackers aim DENIAL of SERVICE attacks at your mobile</datesource>
		<body>
			<line>"A security consultant who works for Telefonica has turned up a bug in how Snapchat handles authentication tokens, 
			which enables a denial-of-service attack against users' phones.</line>
			<line>It's a simple enough problem, the tokens should expire, but don't. As a result, one token can be re-used on many machines, 
			and with a little scripting, all those machines can be instructed to send pictures.</line>
			<line>“That could let an attacker send spam to the 4.6 million leaked account list in less than one hour”, Sánchez writes. 
			Or, in a DoS scenario, the machines could be instructed to hose a single user.</line>
			<line>If the DoS is aimed at an iPhone, he says, it will freeze; Android phones don't seem to lock up completely, but “it does 
			slow their speed. It also makes it impossible to use the app until the attack has finished.”</line>
		</body>
		<source><a href="theregister.co.uk/2014/02/10/snapchat_token_bug_creates_dos_attack_for_ios_android/">Source</a></source>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<image><img src="V3.png" alt="V3"/></image>
		<datesource>[05/02/14] V3 - PRISM: GCHQ spies used phishing and DoS attacks against Anonymous hackers</datesource>
		<body>
			<line>"A secret spy unit linked to the UK Government Communications Headquarters (GCHQ) proactively attacked hackers 
			related to the Anonymous collective, according to leaked NSA documents.</line>
			<line>NBC published documents leaked by whistleblower Edward Snowden showing that the group, codenamed the Joint Threat 
			Research Intelligence Group (JTRIG), attempted to shut down and spread information throughout the Anonymous collective.</line>
			<line>The document alleged the unit attempted to phish Anonymous members and launched attacks designed to disrupt and infiltrate 
			its networks as part of an operation called Rolling Thunder.</line>
			<line>The documents show the spies mounted a sophisticated espionage campaign that let intelligence officers phish a number 
			of Anonymous members to extrapolate key bits of information."</line>
		</body>
		<source><a href="http://www.v3.co.uk/v3-uk/news/2327080/prism-gchq-spies-used-phishing-and-dos-attacks-against-anonymous-hackers">Source</a></source>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<image><img src="IBT.jpg" alt="IBT"/></image>
		<datesource>[26/09/13] International Business Times – Spamhaus DDoS Attack: 16-Year-Old London Teenager Arrested In 'World's Biggest Cyber Attack' On Dutch Site</datesource>
		<body>
			<line>"A 16-year-old London youth has been detained in what is being dubbed the “world’s biggest cyber attack.” According to the Evening Standard, 
			the boy was arrested at his home in London in April, but the news became known on Thursday.</line>
			<line>“The suspect was found with his computer systems open and logged on to various virtual systems and forums,” a document on the case seen by 
			the Evening Standard said. “The subject has a significant amount of money flowing through his bank account. Financial investigators are in the 
			process of restraining monies.”"</line>
		</body>
		<source><a href="http://www.ibtimes.com/spamhaus-ddos-attack-16-year-old-london-teenager-arrested-worlds-biggest-cyber-attack-dutch-site">Source</a></source>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<image><img src="IBT.jpg" alt="IBT"/></image>
		<datesource>[19/04/13] International Business Times – Reddit Hit By Malicious DDoS Attack As News Of The Boston Marathon Bombing Suspects Rolled In</datesource>
		<body>
			<line>"Popular social news site Reddit was hit by a malicious distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack on Friday morning, even as Internet users attempted 
			to report on the massive shootout between police officers and suspects of the Boston Marathon bombings that occurred on Monday.</line>
			<line>Although DDoS attacks are known to be caused by overloading Web servers with external communication requests, Reddit was quick to tell users that the 
			attack was not simply too much traffic from users – especially given the circumstances of that early hour, with live updating news on the Boston bombing 
			suspects coming directly from users – but was in fact a “malicious” attack.”</line>
			<line>Reddit has modified a number of its most popular links to read-only mode “due to heavy traffic,” and continues to showcase a banner at the top of the 
			page informing users that “site availability is being impacted by a malicious DDoS attack."</line></body>
		<source><a href="http://www.ibtimes.com/reddit-hit-malicious-ddos-attack-news-boston-marathon-bombing-suspects-rolled-1204463">Source</a></source>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<image><img src="BBC.png" alt="BBC"/></image>
		<datesource>[27/03/13] BBC News – Global internet slows after 'biggest attack in history'</datesource>
		<body>
			<line>"The internet around the world has been slowed down in what security experts are describing as the biggest cyber-attack of its kind in history.</line>
			<line>A row between a spam-fighting group and hosting firm has sparked retaliation attacks affecting the wider internet. Five national cyber-police-forces 
			are investigating the attacks.</line>
			<line>Mr Linford said the attack's power would be strong enough to take down government internet infrastructure. "If you aimed this at Downing Street they 
			would be down instantly," he said. "They would be completely off the internet." He added: "These attacks are peaking at 300 Gbps (gigabits per second). 
			"Normally when there are attacks against major banks, we're talking about 50 Gbps""</line>
		</body>
		<source><a href="http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-21954636">Source</a></source>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<image><img src="CF.png" alt="CF"/></image>
		<datesource>[27/03/13] Cloud Flare – The DDoS That Almost Broke the Internet</datesource>
		<body>
			<line>"On Monday, March 18, 2013 Spamhaus contacted CloudFlare regarding an attack they were seeing against their website spamhaus.org. They signed up for 
			CloudFlare and we quickly mitigated the attack. The attack, initially, was approximately 10Gbps generated largely from open DNS recursors. On March 19, 
			the attack increased in size, peaking at approximately 90Gbps. The attack fluctuated between 90Gbps and 30Gbps until 01:15 UTC on on March 21.</line>
			<line>The attackers were quiet for a day. Then, on March 22 at 18:00 UTC, the attack resumed, peaking at 120Gbps of traffic hitting our network. As we discussed 
			in the previous blog post, CloudFlare uses Anycast technology which spreads the load of a distributed attack across all our data centers. This allowed us to 
			mitigate the attack without it affecting Spamhaus or any of our other customers. The attackers ceased their attack against the Spamhaus website four hours 
			after it started.</line>
			<line>Other than the scale, which was already among the largest DDoS attacks we've seen, there was nothing particularly unusual about the attack to this point. 
			Then the attackers changed their tactics. Rather than attacking our customers directly, they started going after the network providers CloudFlare uses for bandwidth."</line>
		</body>
		<source><a href="http://blog.cloudflare.com/the-ddos-that-almost-broke-the-internet">Source</a></source>
	</article>

</news>
